(low pitch) Victory will be…
(low pitch)… ours!
Shortly before…
(sly) Ladiiieees and gentlemeeeen…Welcome to Pyramid, Queen Cleopatra’s glamorous night club!
(excited squeak)
(excited grunt)
(cheers)
(haughty, to the crowd) Good evening, people of no interest…
The time has come to draw the (with emphasis) event of the year!
(nervous) Mud wrestling, come on, mud wrestling!
(confused grunt)
(obvious) Spooky, there’s only one piece of paper.
(obvious) Where it always says “couples’ dance contest”.
(obvious) Every year.
(sly) But who knows, maybe this year…
Couples’ dance contest!!
(cheers until 1:14)
(screams desperate) Noooooo!!!
(reac)
(acts vague but is a little upset) But Spooky… don’t you want to dance with me?
(sounds fake) Oh no! I really do! It’s just that my style of dance isn’t allowed…
(confused moan)
(encouraging) Every style of dance is allowed!
(disappointed) Ah…Well then…(pretending awesoooome)!!!… (chuckles)
And declaring the winners of the cup will be our own noble Cleopatra! Let the first pair take the floor: Alsah and Ennah, the bickering sisters! (with emphasis) Let the dances begiiiin!!!
(soft moan)
(heartfelt) (excited) A slow dance… my favorite style!
(singing) Yay yay yay!
(singing) Ye ye ye!
(heartfelt) (excited) A silly and catchy pop tune! My favorite style!
(tender) A night of dancing isn’t so bad after all, huh?
(embarassed) Yeeeeah… Well… it’s not mud wrestling, but… I’m sorry!
(screams) Ahhh (REACTIONS)
(shouting) Alsah!
(sincere) Oh, poor things!! They were doing so well!
(disinterested) Disqualified! Let’s move on already, I don’t have all night…
(struggles super hard with the cup) No! They were fantastic! They’ve won! Contest is oveeeer!!! (scolding) And now for some mud wrestling!
Spooky, put the cup away. It’s a dance competition, and it’s not over.
(disappointed grunt) (effort, scared, about to fall moan) (painful grunt) (inhales) (surprised) Heeeey! Look! Their magnificent performance was sabotaged!
Or maybe they just slipped…
(shouting) (in panic) Sabotage!
…on a banana peel!
(proud) SA-BO-TAGE! (desperate) Look at how devastated those sweet little girls are!
(frustrated) (scolding) It’s your fault! Watch where you put your feet!
(frustrated) (angry) No, you’re the one who pushed me!
(thinking) I have to find the culprit… (shouting) this is a case for Spooky Wolf! Assistaaants! (realizes) Oh, you’re already here…
(annoyed) Could you get off the dance floor? We’re next…
(amplified by the microphone) Next couple: Grunt and Jane!
(to Grunt and Jane) But Alsah and Ennah’s dance was sabotaged! (intense) There’s a mystery to solve!
The only mystery here is: how long since this place was last  tidied up!
(annoyed) And now boss, if you don’t mind…(grunts) (grunts x 6) (exhales) (relieved) Ah… finally!
(Giggles)
(impressed) Oooh!
Well you guys follow me anyway, I know who did it!
But Spooky… it was just an unfortunate accident! (gasps) / (in a low voice) (confused) But why are we dressed up like cows, Spooky?
(grunts) / (proud grunt) (grunts) (grunts) (chuckles) (grunts)
(proud moan) / (moans) (moans)
(in a low voice, sly) Nothing goes more unnoticed than a cow in a night club! It’s the per-fect disguise!
Hi, Spooky.
(in panic) Cover blown, plan B! (defiant) Here we are dear Mr. Trillionaire, as rich as he is cheap!
(shushes) (REAC)
(confused) Huh? (confused grunt) / (confused grunt) / (confused grunt) (confused grunt) / (dissaproving grunt)
(confused grunt x7) / (confused grunt) / (dissaproving grunt)
(with emphasis) Confess! (desperate) You ruined those poor little girls’ dance! (scolding) Just so your daughter, the super spoiled Princess Prom, could win!
(shouting) (angry) Hey! My daughter isn’t spoiled! (REAC)
Daddy, I want a gold bar, but one that you can eat.
Here you are, sweetie. (chuckles) And anyway, it couldn’t have been me, I bet everything on someone else after I saw them training…
(confused grunt)
(moaning singing) (effort grunt)
(shouting) Garden gnomes don’t…(drowning) blbl…swim…(sinking and blowing bubbles) Blblblbl!
(dreamy) That gnome, Snotty… He has a unique style!
Yeah, you really did’t need to sabotage anything, Trillytrilly, those two have victory in their grasp!
Not guilty!
(angry) Hey, who ate my appetizers?
(grunts)
(confused) But if Pig-raw is there… then who are you???
(moaning singing)
(effort grunts)
Come on, let’s think about our performance!  Are you still convinced that it was a sabotage?
(uncomfortable moans)
Yes, I’m completely sure!
(worried) It’s not that you’re looking for an excuse not to dance with me… are you?
(very fast) (defensive) Whaaaat?! Absolutely not but honestly no no no no no, also because then you and me… it would be great… (very embarrassed) buuuut…
(worried)…But???
To be honest (stutters) IIIII… I don’t know how to say it… (shouting) Nooo!
(grunts) (grunts) (effort grunt) / (painful grunt)
(screams) / (whimpers)
(gasp).. (cheer)
(gasp)
(OFF) (gasp).. (cheer)
(off) (gasps)
(closed mouth gasp)
(gasps)
(effort grunt) (effort grunt) (chuckles)
(cheers)
(thumbs down) (annoyed) Disqualified!!! And you can pay me back for the chandelier!!!
(surprised) Spooky! You were right! Someone wants to sabotage the dance contest!
(confused) Huh? / (confused moan)
(grunts) Sabotageee! (grunts)
(condescending, in a soft voice) Grunt… no one was sabotaged… (emphatic, pointing at them) except Alsah and Ennah! Never fear girls, I’ll solve the case! NOTHING will distract me from… (confused) Huh?
(announces) Next couple! Princess Prom and Amazing, the very haaaandsome unicorn!
(excited) Oooh, I want to see them so much!
(excited moan)
Rx
(in a low voice, very mean) Either we win or I’ll have Daddy’s superhero send you to Pluto! // (chuckles)
(nervous chuckle) (nervous moan) (grunts) / (chuckles)
Rx
(confused moan) (shouting) Help! It itches! It itches! (nervous moan)
(shouting) Ahhh
(grunts) (gasps)
Disqualified!
(scratching) (nervous) Forgive me Prom, but think I have fleas! (whimpers)
(annoyed grunt)
(scolding) (shouting) You ruined everything! I hate you! (whimpers)
(serious) More sabotage…
Sabotage? Naaaah! You should have a shower every once in a while my friend, there’s a bit of a smell…
(defensive) But that’s coming from the cow!
Super-fluss, superfluous handyman superhero, you know what you have to do!
Ready for Pluto?
(nervous) But… (screams)
(grunts) (excited) Oooh, it’s a fleeeaaa circus!!!
Precisely! A circus… of fleas! It’s an obvious sabota…
(finishes the word) Super entertainment created by Cleopatra! Like that!
Get me out of here! Us garden gnomes can’t swi… blblblbl
(annoyed) I was going to say “Sabotage”!
(excited) Ooooh! Tightrope-walking fleas! (considers) But I don’t have time for fun right now! I have to solve the case of the banana peel! (surprised) (excited) Nooo, there are clown fleas too!! (clears throat) Errrm, I meant: we have to find Alsah and Ennah’s saboteur!
(shouts after Spooky) (scolding) Don’t you get it?! Someone is sabotaging everyone!
(jovial, wise guy) No no! It was  only the banana!
(grunts)
(sighs, then to Grunt, pragmatic) Let’s get to work solving the (with emphasis) REAL case!
Affirmative, Jane!
(quick) Zero clues, zero clues, zero clues, (excited) oooh a potato chip! (eats it) (with mouth full) Crispy-crunchy! Zero clues, zero clues… Hey Cherry! But you’ve become a giant! If that’s the case, we can’t dance together anymore, too baaaad…
(determined) Spooky! Just be honest with me! You don’t want to dance with me! I won’t be offended!
Well, I mean…
It’s no big deal!
Whatever you say…
(annoyed) (scolding) Can’t you drop it?!
(confused moan) Oooh, I saw a super-clue right over there, byeeee!!! Bye to you too Cherry’s conscience! (chuckles)
(confused moan) / (relieved sight)
(relieved sight)
And nooooow….. the last couple in the contest… (grandiose) the loopy lupine Spooky and the red-as-a-rose Cherry!
(calling out) Spooky, it’s our turn. (confused) Spooky?! Are you pretending to be a mummy so you don’t have to dance?
(in a small voice, moving his mouth a little) No.
(calling out) You moved. And you spoke.
(in a small voice) No I didn’t.
(scolding) You did it again.
(in a small voice) It wasn’t me.
(frustrated grunt) (louder) Look, a flying pizza!!! / (frustrated grunt)
(confused) Mmm.? (excited) Where, where?!!!! (nervous chuckle) / All right… I have to tell you something… I really want to dance with you Cherry… also because I…
(scolding) No! / (with emphasis) Tell her, tell her! / The second! (scolding) You can’t say the first!
But you see, the fact is that… (confused) What?! The first thing or the second?!
(intense) Cherry…(doing wrestler poses) Mud wrestling! (corrects himself) I mean… (yelled, desperate) I don’t know how to dance! (pants)
(intense) Yes…?
(jovial) That’s why I gave him dance lessons! (chuckles) Ho-ho-ho!
(happily surprised) Santa Claus?! (chuckles) I didn’t know you could dance!
(effort grunt) (effort grunt) (effort grunt)
(thinking) Mmm, (disappointed) actually, I don’t know how to dance…
The couple must take the floor or they’ll be disqualified!
(grunts) (panic squeak) / (excited moan)
(encouraging) Follow my steps and everything will be fine. Do you trust me? / (frustrated grunt) / (surprised moan)
OK… (very quick) Actually no, I’m leaving, I’m changing planet, byeeee! / (disappointed) OK…
(soft voice) Guys, keep an eye out! The saboteur is still at large!
(confused) Huh? (grunts) (affirming grunts)
(cuts in, wise guy) Naaah… all a coincidence! Only Alsah and Ennah were sabota…(whimpers)  (low voice) I’m scared… (talks following the rhythm) I-can’t-dance! (very surprised) Hey! I can dance!
Of course you can dance! It’s the power of lo…
(shushes) Shhh! You can’t say it!
(excited) (surprised) Cool! My conscience has a conscience!
(happy) Well done Spooky!
(soft voice) See anything?
(soft voice) Nothing at all! But they’re surely about to strike!
(looks up, shocked) But it’s… a…
(appalled) A… a…
Here comes the little boat, and here’s the… (surprised) (frustrated) Hey, where’s my…
(with emphasis) (progressively increasing tone) Rub-ber duck-ie!
(whimpers)
(encouraging) Come on Spooky! Don’t give up now! We’re almost there!
First the investigation… then the dance… I’m exhausted! I need another energy banana!
(confused) Another?
Yeah, sure! / I already ate a banana earlier! During the performance of…(gulps) (exhales) (chuckles) / (realizes) (in panic) Heeeey! But then I…!
(scolding) Don’t say it don’t say it!
(confused) (surprised) Spooky! What’s happening to you?!
(whimpers)
(chuckles excited)
Huh? (chuckles excited)
(whimpers)
(nervous chuckle)
(shouting) (calling out) Spooky!
(shouting) (calling out) Cherry! Ha!
(scared scream)
(scared scream) (painful grunt)
(annoyed) Is anyone going to actually finish in this dance contest?!
(scared) What a little-giaaant duck! Thanks Grunt! The case is solved! It’s true, someone is sabotaging all the dances, not just Alsah and Ennah’s… And that someone is (in panic) ME!
(gasp)
(gasps)
(melodramatic) I threw the banana peel! I made the chandelier fall! I unleashed the fleas! I…
Spooky, I’m pretty sure you can stop at the banana.
(thinking) Hmm… you’re right. (tender) It was a silly mistake! (humble) I apologize…but the ones who have to apologize to everyone else… are you!
(gasps)
(gasps) (surprised) Whaaaat?!!! / (gasps) / (gasps) / (annoyed grunt)
(convinced) It’s the most classic motive: revenge!
(psyched) Yeeeaaah!!!
You were sabotaged, so now you’re sabotaging everyone!
(defiant) Prove it, if you can! // (10:04) (gasps)
(evil chuckle) Hm?
(confident) Eeeaasy! There’s someone here who witnessed absolutely everything! (chuckles) // Did you hear the cow?! It said it was them! Alsah and Ennah!
(gasps)
(surprised) (incomprehensible, line not on script)
(nervous chuckles)
(incredulous) But since when do we all understand cowish?
(sly) These things always happen in cartoons!
(chuckles)
GUILTY!
Sorry! (then mean to Ennah) It’s my sister’s fault, she’s very competitive… Hm?/ (angry grunts)
(mean to Alsah) (gasp)... me? You’re the one who couldn’t accept that we were eliminated! (angry grunts)
Plot Twist! I officially declare the contest is totally messed up! We have to start all over again!
(angry) (annoyed) Oh no! That’s enough! Mummies, throw these people out of my nightclub! (surprised) (confused) Hey, what’s…?
[10:10:37:22][00:00:00]TRILLIONAIRE
Rx
(reac) (moved moan)
(surprised) Hey wait, don’t throw them out anymore… we have the winners! Bring in the cup!
(cheers until 10:54)
(chheer)
(excited grunt) (chuckles)
(emotional) Well, too bad. We didn’t win… But it was still really nice, right? / A perfect dance…
(blushes slightly) Suuuure! A case solved…(chuckles) (in a crescendo of embarrassment) You know Cherry I… I…
(in panic) No no no don’t say it!
(excited) Yes…?
(excited) I love the fleeaa circus! Yeeaah! (excited) There are trapeze artist fleas toooo?! (chuckles)
(very angry) Blblblblblblb!
End of Eps.