This ice cream is so good, right friends?!
Yes, buddy!  Especially the very red strawberryyyy!!!
(REACTIONS)
(gasp) What's happening?  You disappeaaared!..  But as long as I have my ice cream, I...  ...as long as I have a little sand in the top half of the hourglass, I won't be really sad!..  Well, now I'm sad...  So super-mega-sad.. and now I'm disappearing tooooo...
A few hours earlier...
(REACTION)
Well well well! Penalty card for Pig-raw!  "Pig-raw... make the sound of a pig... or lose everything!"
Boooo, that didn't sound like a pig at all!  Too bad, you lose everything! Mwahahaha!!!
Hey! What do you mean? That was an exemplary pig noise! (REACTIONS)
Oh, come on! To win "The bad guy!" game, you have to be the best at being bad! (REACTIONS)
Rx
It's called "The Bad Guy"! Not "The sneaky cheater!" and you're cheating boss!
Grunt's right, Spooky!
Come on, let's all try to be mature!
(REACTIONS)
(REACTIONS) I'm mature! The game is mine, so I say game over! Now I'm going to bed for the evening! And I'm not even going to say goodnight. No goodnight!
(REACTION)
Oooh, how stupid, Spooky went the wrong direction! No goodnight again!
Good moooorning!!!  Actually, no, not good morning, I'm still offended.  Even if I don't remember what for.  But what does it matter, good moooorning!!! (REACTION) Oh, you're not even talking to me, huh? You all still offended-ed? Or maaaaybe it's just that... You aren't there?!  Yessss, that's it.
(LAUGHS) (scared) (10) No. (LAUGHS)
Hey Snotty, have you seen the guys?
Why are you snickering through clenched teeth?  Did you think of something hilarious?
No. (LAUGHS)
You keep your little secrets, I have my own! In fact on just came to mind and I'm not going to tell you... (LAUGHS) (LAUGHS) (LAUGHS) (LAUGHS) Alright, I'll tell you my secret:  we had an argument last night.  They've probably gone off to take a secret stroll alone,  just to disrespect me.  Come on, let's go search for them!
(LAUGHS) (LAUGHS) (LAUGHS)
Hey, what are you doing?! Let me go! (REACTIONS) Let me outta here! (REACTIONS)
Come oooon! I don't want to go by myself! So, you going to tell me your little secret!
There's mushy, stinky stuff in here!
That'll be the bananas from last year! Gruuunt! Jane! Pig-raw! They aren't here! (REACTIONS) There's an ice cream cone here, but no one to eat it...mysterioouuus...
The real mystery is why everyone has disappeared...
Oh, right. That's really curious...  But of cooouurse! They've organized a mega-party at Cherry's diner to make it up to me!
There is no party, you foolish wolmmmmmmm! (REACTIONS)
Oh yes yes, party party! Let's go before they finish the potato chiiiips!!! (REACTIONS) Mmm... pistachio and asphalt, my favorite!
You see?! No party!
But then it must be a surprise party! I know you're hiiiding! I'm gonna fiiiind you!
(grunt) There is no cursed surprise party! EVERYONE HAS DISAPPEARED!
Well then... this is a case for Spooky Wolf!  Ooooh, but it's so cool that we can do whatever we liiiike!!!!
Oooh, if Granny could see me...  but she's not here! It's so great being all aloooone!!!!
One week later...
So guys, what do you say we order a pizza? Sure, boss!  OK Spooky!  Pig sound! Here comes the pizza! Thank you Cherry.  Mmm, my favorite...  Oh Cherry... now that you are here in front of me, I have to tell you that... that I... I lo... (REACTIONS)
Spooky!
Cherry!!! (REACTIONS)
Boss!
(REACTIONS)
Guys! You've come back!  Of course, you took things a little too far disappearing for an entire week and becoming see-through...
(REACTION) Semitransparent.
Sssemi-transpa-thing... Just becauseee...
I mean, technically we're not semitransparent...
Can I finiiiish?! Semitransparent just because we had an argument...  but I forgive yoooouuuu!!!
Forget the fight!  In order to be able to talk to you, I created a portal using a hairclip, a yo-yo, and a used piece of chewing gum.
Wow! (REACTIONS) Ow! But where are you?!
But it won't last!
At home!  Just in another dimension!
(REACTIONS)
Whaaaat?!  All this because we fought?!
The fight doesn't matter!!! Something mysterious happened and YOU...  ooh, it's time for "Open Heart", my favorite medical soap! (REACTIONS)
Oooh, that's true! (REACTION)
I can't transplant another heart into the woman I love! What if she doesn't love me anymore?
(REACTIONS)
The portal is closing!  You have to figure out who it was and bring us back!
No, wait!
Spooky!  Hey! Is that monstrosity me?!
Noooo! Don't worry, Cherry! I'll bring you home! Meanwhile, you could at least reattach my arm!
Come back to me oh brothers, come back to me...(REACTION).. (REACTION)
Snottyyyy! I found them!  Heeeey, what's all that stuff?
Nothing. Did you find them? Where are they?
In another dimensiioooon!
As I suspected...  OK wolf, but now I have things to do...
Of cooouuurse you have things to do! We have to find out who the bad guy is who sent them there! They must still be here in Fantaville! Come on, let's go, apprentice detective!
I'm not your apprentice!
OK...  valet?
No. No. No. Mmh...  Let's go with valet.(REACTION) Watch it, wolf, I'm not going back in that stinking thing ever again.(REACTIONS)
Butler? Squire? Orr... horse? And so velvet it shall be!
Shock the mad scientist... not guilty!
(REACTIONS)
Monster of the Dark... not guilty!
Fan... not guilty!
(REACTIONS)
Unlock this door! I want to go back to Villa Lobos!  I! Have! Things! To! Do!
But don't you understand, valet?! If the bad guy is still in Fantaville, but they're nowhere around... it means that...  The bad guy is meeee!  I was a bad guy  while playing the Bad Guy and now everyone has gone away! It's my faaauult!
(REACTION)
Stop blubbering! You're getting me all wet!  It wasn't you, you foolish wolf! (REACTIONS) No! And I'm not your friend!
Really...?  Thanks, old buddy!  Play a quick game?! (REACTIONS) But if it wasn't me, this means thaaaaat...Guys!!! You're here again! You're at the diner too! (REACTIONS) Ooh and there's Amazing!
Hey boss!
(REACTIONS)
Yes! The portal only works when we and you are in the same place!
Hi, that baby looks like Snotty! (REACTION)
And Granny too!
Who ate all of my tacos?!
No... i... de... a... pah!
Pah, that portal doesn't work well.
Bye bye Granny!!! (REACTION)
There's Snotty!... Hey, is that a baby carriage?!
There's Snotty! Guys, Look!
Friends! My friends! Stay calm, I'll get you all back! I just have to reverse this enchantment! (REACTIONS)
Oooooooh, have you hurt yourself poor little one? There there there now, everything passes, in the meantime what about a nice story? But yooouuu're the one who's going to tell it!  Because it was you who made everyone disappear!
(grunt) Yeeaaah... but I won't tell you how!  Actually, to make you jealous of my genius, I'll tell you everything!.. I was fed up of seeing you going in and out of Villa Lobos, which should be my house, with your stupid smile!.. That day I decided that if I couldn't have the house... at least I would get rid of your smile!
(REACTIONS)
So.. I put a spell on you with the garden gnomes' runestones.
What kind of stoooones!?!
Don't come into my flashback! Runestones! The ones you saw me using in the garden!
Aaaaah!
(REACTION) Now, where was I...
And what's a flashback?
Go awaaay!!!
With the stones, I was going to make your friends disappear...
(REACTIONS)
But you're friends with everyone, you quick-to-smile wolf!
(Hums)... Ooooh and now who can I play with?!.. (Screams)
With me!
...so everyone disappeared, even my gnome friends!
(REACTIONS)
Guilty!
But why didn't you disappear, seeing as you're my friend?!
I told you I'm not your friend!  And in any case, whoever casts the enchantment can't be affected, everyone knows that!
Oh.  You see?! You're my friieend! OK, OK Snotty, let's clear things up once and for all then. I don't like you and you don't like me.  I mean right at this moment, because you did a veeery bad thing, otherwise normally  hey, don't worry, super-friends, I'd never want you to think that... but we have to work together if we want to bring our friends back here!
(REACTION)
Get on with it!!!
OK...
Did I hear "OOOOK!"? Booooom! The Detective and the vassal! Duo of the yeeaar!!! (REACTIONS)
(REACTION) Actually, it was valet!.. Here are the sacred runestones.. I tried many reverse enchantments but none of them worked!.. I used all the magical phrases I know.. and I joined the stones in every way possible but...
Aloha 'Aina!!! (REACTIONS) Aaatchooo! Oops! How embarrassing! Oooh! Tug of war! Great idea! . Wait a moment... rope? Of course!
Drop the garden gnomes' sacred runestones immediately! Cut that out right this instant! (REACTIONS)
So are you going to tell me what you're doing?!
I'm waiting for the portal to reopen! You heard Jane, right? The portal only opens when we and they are in the same place!
And why should they be at home now?
Because it's time for Jane's favorite medical soap.
The patient's heart has a problem!  It's in love... with me!
And what do you need the runestones for?!
I throw the rope to the other side of the portal, they grab onto it, and we pull them back over to this side!
You were about to say  "that's the most idiotic thing I've ever heard!" But instead, thinking about it carefully...
That's the most idiotic thing I've ever heard!
(REACTIONS)
Hey! We're here! It opened! (REACTIONS)
Don't disturb me!
The soap's on!
Grab onto iiiit!!!
(REACTIONS)
Erm... it's just that there's such a resemblance!  Grab onto iiiit!!!
(REACTION)
(REACTIONS)
(REACTIONS) Ugh! Right during the kissing scene too!!!
Pull, Spooky! (REACTIONS)
(REACTIONS)
You see?! It doesn't work!
(REACTION) You're sooo pessimistic! Come on, say one of your magic phrases!
I've already tried them all!
You'll figure it out, you must have said something like  "Dark powers of the darkest caverns..." I know what it needs!  Come now, valet, say  "Long live the friends-ends-ends la la la la la!"
I will never say any nonsense of the sort!
Oooooh sorry, I thought you wanted to get your gnome friends back here!
The portal's re-closing!
(REACTIONS)
OK, OK, I'll say it!  Long live the friends-ends-ends la la la la la!
Spooky! (REACTIONS)
(REACTIONS)
Booooss!!! (REACTIONS)
Snotty...?
Hm.. Guys! (LAUGHS).. (crash)
Garden gnomes friends forever!
Hooray, we're baaaack!.. Aaaahhh, the sun burns vampires!!!
Aaaaaaaaaah!!!!
(REACTION)
Another week later...
(REACTIONS) See? I'm not smiling.
I get it. It's fine. Go.
No, because I wouldn't like you to think that...
So are we all good, friend?
I'm not your...! (REACTION) We're good.. Go!.. (grunt)
OK OK, I get it, I can't stay here all day waiting for you to give me a high five! Huh! I'm a busy wolf me!
Spooky, I get that you were really worried... but is this really necessary?!
(REACTIONS) Oh yes! I don't want you to go away ever again! Especially you!
(REACTIONS)